You're mid-task, focused and in rhythm. Your inbox is full,
but you are on track with your to-do list,
and in the background someone is waiting on you.
Then suddenly, something you were counting on just fell through.
Before you do anything, what is the first thing you notice?
In your body? In your thoughts? What feelings do you have?
Do you have an urge to do something?
There's no right answer to what you just noticed.
Don't change it. Just catch it.
What you noticed is data. The signal your system sends when the unexpected happens,
before you've decided to do anything.
For the rest of the season, every time something falls through, try to catch that signal before you act on it.
There is nothing to fix yet. Just become aware.